[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[theme music playing]
A LOVE OTHER THAN YOURS
[theme music concludes]
ALL PERSONS, LOCATIONS, RELIGIONS,
INCIDENTS, AND ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS HAVE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER PARENTAL SUPERVISION
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY WITH EXPERT ADVICE AND COOPERATION
[actors smooching]
[gentle piano music playing]
[walkie-talkie button clicks]
[Ho-sik] I think the Moon Donut
should go over there.
Let's just swap it with Choo Choo Kong.
-[Sang-hun] Swap it? Sure.
-[Ho-sik] Like, further back.
I don't like it.
Chili Crunch has gotta lead.
-You're a fan of the Moon Donut.
-[sighs]
They're both in different sales leagues.
Hey, Chili Crunch should be in the front.
-The front now?
-[Ho-sik] No, no.
-Hmm, perfect.
-Now you covered it too much.
-[sighs] Where should we put this?
-And Hot Choco Chips won't fit.
It used to be our company's
biggest hit product.
Uh, how about putting it
right in the center? [sighs]
Hatguma just launched.
They look nice next to each other.
Let's drag it over there
and see how it looks.
-[Ho-sik] What are you-- Uh, no.
-[Sang-hun] Just grab the bottom.
[Ho-sik] Don't move it.
I like it where it is.
BROTHER CLEANING
[music fades]
-[groans]
-Is Namgung answering your calls?
Don't bother him.
Namgung deserves to be left alone.
He's gotta deal with Mi-do, you know?
-Yeah, right. Look who's talking.
-[gasps] Oh, my God! Don't do that!
You cried and cried
because you couldn't afford
to get married,
and what did you do
when your sister got the money?
You ended up divorced. [laughs mockingly]
-What a pathetic loser. [laughs]
-Why are you bringing that up again?
People are gonna think
you bought me a house or something.
You only gave me
a measly five million won.
[gasps] "Measly five million"? Hey!
-[funky music playing]
-There's a huge difference
between someone with 100 million
lending you five million
and someone with ten million
doing the same. Stop it!
And if someone like your sister
only has five and a half
and lends you five,
you seriously don't get it?
What I took isn't even close!
Never mind I handed you
all that I had, okay?
That five million won
wasn't just five million.
It was all I had then, you know?
It'd be equal to 500 million.
You have no right to use
the word "measly" in that context, got it?
And didn't I pay you back, huh?
Every last won.
God, did you even hear
a word I just said, huh?
If five million was worth 500,
then you should've gave me 500 million,
-you idiot!
-You loan shark!
Yeah, sure, I'm a loan shark,
but you're a dumbass!
-You're scamming your own brother?
-Just stop it already!
-[sighs] Mm…
-[sighs]
I'm gonna throw up.
-[exhales deeply, gulps]
-[music fades]
[bottles clinking]
[sighs]
[Mi-do]  To my dearly, dearly, dearly,
dearly, dearly beloved Nam-gu-ding.
[sniffles]
[Mi-do]  You must be happy.
After crushing on me for such a long time,
you finally got me.
[sniffles]
[Mi-do]  You better treat me right.
You've still got a lot to learn,
so keep working at it.
-Are you freaking kidding me? [grunts]
-[cell phone vibrating]
[Namgung sighs]
YEONG-DO
-What's up?
-[Yeong-do]  Man, we're in big trouble.
-Mi-do just disappeared.
-What?
-[bright music playing]
-[Yeong-do]  God, she drives me crazy.
Where could she be?
Bro, can you please come over?
We're at a… Wait, wait, where was I?
Wait, wait, hold on.
Why would I do that?
Lee Mi-do and I broke up, you know that.
Check the playground. Focus on the slide.
[Yeong-do]  Come on, you two
are gonna get back together anyway.
Aren't you a bit worried about her?
If something happens to her--
If something happens to her,
tell me why I should care.
Turns out we're total strangers now.
I'm moving on and I'll… I'll…
I'll join a dating app
or go on blind dates.
I'll even go on a dating show,
and I'll like it.
[groans]
[bright music continues]
[sighs]
[groans]
TO MY DEEPLY BELOVED NAMGUNG-TUSH.
[sighs, groans]
[groans]
-[exhales deeply]
-[music concludes]
[sighs]
[clears throat]
Is volume eight of  Slam Dunk
at your place?
[breathes deeply]
[elevator bell dings]
[intriguing music playing]
[groans]
[keypads beeping]
[door locks beeping]
2. CAN WE EVER BE STRANGERS?
[music concludes]
NON-DISCLOSURE
AND RELATIONSHIP TERMINATION AGREEMENT
[Tae-seung] Here's the non-disclosure
agreement stating
you won't reveal your meeting
with the CEO.
[sighs]
SIGNATURE
[sighs] Hmm.
Very well, I'll be taking over
and finalizing
Director Lee Mi-do's case as well.
You heard, right?
-[whimsical instrumental music playing]
-[sobbing loudly]
-[grunts, sobs]
-[cell phone vibrates]
[Tae-seung]
This is Attorney Han Tae-seung.
I heard through Producer Oh Yeon-ju
that you declined.
Would you be able to meet one more time?
-I kindly await your response.
-[sobs]
-[cell phone vibrates]
-[Tae-seung]  If we go to trial,
you'll lose money, time,
and emotional energy,
-not to mention your reputation.
-[muffled sobbing]
[Tae-seung]  Why would you choose
such a difficult path?
I await your call.
-[sniffles]
-[cell phone vibrates]
[Tae-seung]  Hi again.
I've handled the mediation request
you filed with
the Film Industry Grievance Board.
If this goes public,
it'll be bad for both of us.
-Look forward to hearing from you.
-I hate this asshole.
[grunts]
-[grunting]
-[cell phone vibrates]
Hmm?
25TH
I HAVE SOMETHING IMPORTANT THIS MONTH
CAN YOU SEND IT A WEEK EARLY?
[music concludes]
[exhales deeply]
MY DEAR DICTATOR VER. 3
[soft instrumental music playing
over speakers]
[door opens]
-[door closes]
-[breathes deeply]
[Tae-seung sighs]
I waited for you to answer,
but you didn't.
I figured out your usual haunts,
so I did some research beforehand,
and here I am.
Ahyeon Library, Hanpung Bookstore,
Haneul Park, Jake Coffee in Gongdeok,
Nemo's Cafe, and… [inhales sharply]
…grilled fish at Yeoju Auntie's. Wow.
The charcoal-grilled mackerel is fire.
[inhales sharply]
You really should sign the settlement.
We'll guarantee
that you get 30 percent copyright.
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
Are you married, Counselor?
Why do you ask?
-So, it wasn't this idiot.
-"This idiot"?
[indistinct chatter]
[pen scrawling]
[sighs deeply]
[Mi-do]  Show up like this again,
and you're dead.
[scoffs]
[music stops]
[door opens]
[Tae-seung] Is it because your mom owns
a building in Yeonhui-dong?
Wow, you are something else.
Well, I need to know who I'm dealing with.
In this business, we call it
a background check or due diligence.
Your oldest brother owns
a drain cleaning company.
The youngest was
the first Korean free diver
to set a national record
in constant weight.
And your longtime boyfriend…
Oh, you guys just broke up.
[gasps] Was it because he found out?
[sighs] Wow, that scumbag.
Piece of shit, honestly.
You don't abandon a girl
at her lowest, right?
[Tae-seung over recording]
Well, I need to know who I'm dealing with.
-[quirky music playing]
-[Tae-seung]  In this business,
we call it a background check
or due diligence.
Your oldest brother owns
a drain cleaning com--
Unauthorized background check
on a civilian.
Illegal interference in a mediation.
Threats made against a family.
Inciting fear under the guise of a deal.
This will help in court, right?
Well, thanks.
Let's add one more to that.
Property damage.
-[grunts]
-[cell phone crunching]
[exhales]
[sighs]
Well, I'll buy you a new phone
and send it to you today.
[music concludes]
[sighs] Hmm.
[exhales] Listen…
I'm really busy with work lately,
so I wanted to settle this trivial case
and be done,
which is why I was being nice to you.
[scoffs] And you're making this difficult.
Since you want it so badly,
I'll see you in court.
I really hope you're ready.
-[Mi-do grunts]
-[gasps]
-[quirky instrumental music playing]
-[breathes heavily]
[gasps softly]
Send me the bill.
[panting] Oh, and make sure
to get the latest model.
A white phone with one tera of storage.
[music concludes]
[indistinct chatter]
[Su-a]  I know the reason
there was an issue with the fourth sample.
-If you want to know, I can tell you.
-[light instrumental music playing]
On the 9th at noon,
over a bowl of Pyongyang  naengmyeon.
I'll be waiting there.
[inhales deeply] Uh, um…
[groans, grunts] Damn it!
-Huh? Huh? Why are you here?
-[sighs]
Ah, jeez, you're so impatient.
Is it because of the sample schedule?
[grunts playfully] Gotcha.
-[Namgung] Can you talk?
-[Ho-sik] Huh?
[Namgung] Come on, let's have a chat.
[Su-a] I guess you forgot our plans today.
[music concludes]
Ah.
I never really said
that I was gonna be there, did I?
Well, no. But there was a difference
between the lab and factory samples.
I heard you were curious about it.
You visited the farms
asking questions, didn't you?
I did. You're right.
But let's just say I don't have the fire
to dive into sticky situations. Hmm.
I look young,
but I'm 35, you know. [chuckles softly]
Hmm. Is that the actual reason?
Of course. After the age of 35,
you start losing muscle mass.
And you're considered too old
to get job subsidies
or national allowance.
It'd be wise
to start taking good care of myself.
Basically, stay out of trouble.
I want to work here,
avoiding trouble until I retire.
That's the reason.
We're producing
with imported sweet potatoes too.
[whimsical instrumental music playing]
[inhales sharply]
I'll pretend you never said that.
I did say it.
And I never heard it.
[inhales deeply]
Of course, I apologize.
I guess I'm asking
too much of the wrong person.
I see what you mean.
[exhales sharply]
[Su-a] The Hatguma Chips?
Texture is bad too.
Especially the sweet and spicy combo.
Absolutely disgusting batch.
[exhales sharply]
-[music fades]
-By the way, Mr. Yoon asked me
to send over the bidding plan
first thing tomorrow.
-Really?
-Someone broke into his house.
He's going to the police.
He said they forced the lock.
-For real?
-[Sang-hun] Yeah.
[door closes]
[door lock beeping]
-[Namgung sighs]
-[funky instrumental music playing]
[card machine beeps]
[customer] Doesn't work?
Is the machine broken?
[owner] Oh, why would it be broken?
It worked fine earlier.
-[alarm beeping]
-[Sang-hun] Dang it.
-What's wrong with it?
-[alarm beeping]
-[Sang-hun] Oh, shoot.
[alarm beeping]
[car alarm honking]
[car alarm honking echoes]
-[scanner alarm beeping]
-[sighs]
Not again. Dang it.
[scanner alarm continues beeping]
-[Sang-hun] Seriously?
-Hey!
-[dramatic musical sting]
-[gulps]
Didn't I tell you to fix that thing?
-[funky instrumental music continues]
-You didn't, sir.
I told you many times in my head.
Go fix that now.
[music concludes]
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[sentimental piano music playing]
Wait…
HONDURAS KARAOKE
-[dramatic pop music playing]
-[Mi-do, in Korean]  ♪ I pushed you away ♪
♪ Only after love has left ♪
♪ Do we realize? ♪
♪ Why did I wander
When you were right beside me? ♪
♪ Now I finally know the… ♪
-[music stops]
-[in English] Ah, shit. [sighs]
Listen, I thought it through.
If you and Namgung are breaking up,
I think I should take his side.
Mm-hmm, right?
You traitor.
-[groans, sighs]
-You'd think Namgung birthed him,
like he's his son.
Yeah, he kind of is.
They've known each other since he was two.
[can lid pops]
I'm really done with Namgung.
I won't see him again.
And I don't need your pity
so you can stop.
Listen here. Don't flatter yourself.
I'm not here as your friend.
-I'm here as a producer.
-[scoffs]
[Yeon-ju] I came here to talk you
into accepting the settlement,
but I can see you're in no state
to discuss this.
Good luck with the lawsuit.
We'll do what we can.
And this isn't as your friend or producer,
but just as a fellow human being…
Mm-mm, save it.
Please go back to Namgung,
for your own good.
[poignant piano music playing]
I'm never getting back together with him.
I don't want to hate him anymore.
And I don't want to be hated either.
Hmm.
[chuckles softly]
[gulps]
[door lock beeps]
She's so lazy.
[door lock chimes]
[door lock beeps]
-[wind chimes tinkling]
-[sighs]
[sighs]
She doesn't even care about the fine dust.
[music fades]
[sighs]
[sighs] She should really clean up.
Jeez, how can she live like this?
She didn't do her laundry.
[inhales sharply]
[sighs]
-[chuckles softly]
-[whimsical piano music playing]
Oh, shit.
[panting] Really now, bro?
-[cups clinking]
-[keypad beeping]
[gasps]
[mutters, groans]
Um…
-Hello.
-Hmm…
[music concludes]
-Hey, my charger.
-[exhales]
We broke up
and I want my stuff back, you know?
-[quirky instrumental music playing]
-[jacket unzipping]
[mutters, grunts]
[groans]
-[music fades]
-[grunts, groans]
[groans]
[tender guitar music playing]
[whimpers, sobs]
[sniffles, whimpers]
[sobs]
Uncle… [sniffles] …you're such a jerk.
[sobs, whimpers]
[sniffles, sobs]
[mutters]
[whimpers]
[groans softly]
[exhales]
[sighs]
SEO JU-HYEOK
-[music fades]
-[cell phone ringing]
Ju-hyeok, listen, you can't just--
[Tae-seung over cell phone]  Song Hae-na.
Han Tae-seung? You have his phone?
SONG HAE-NA
[Hae-na]  I wanna talk
to Ju-hyeok one last time.
-Please, I really need to.
-No, you can't. I'm sorry.
And I'm going to have to ask you
to stop confusing the genres.
You're in a soap opera, yet you're acting
like it's a romance. [scoffs]
-It's kind of sad.
-You're not getting away with this.
I will stop you from doing this.
All I ask is that you don't get
your revenge on a Thursday or Friday.
I have a couple of meetings.
Good talking to you.
[exhales deeply]
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
JAEKANG LAW FIRM
[cell phone ringing]
[automated voice]
The person you are calling is unavailable.
-Please leave your message.
-[inhales deeply, sighs]
Ju-hyeok,
I'm not a little girl. [chuckles]
Don't worry about me.
You're doing business. [chuckles]
Just wrap up your work
and I'll see you soon.
[chuckles] I love you.
-[grunts]
-[lipstick clattering]
That color doesn't suit you.
[tense music continues]
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
Oh, shit.
[cell phone vibrating]
ACTRESS SONG HAE-NA
[music intensifies]
Where the hell are you, huh?
Is this a joke?
[Hae-na]  I slipped something fun
into Kang Ji-yeon's bag earlier.
Pictures of Ju-hyeok and me at the hotel.
-Hmm. Funny, isn't it?
-[sighs]
Ms. Song…
-stop doing things you'll regret.
-I'm curious.
I wonder how well Seo Ju-hyeok's dog
can clean up his mess.
[inhales sharply, sighs]
-[sighs]
-[cell phone vibrates]
[dramatic musical sting]
DIRECTOR LEE MI-DO
[music fades]
-You're awfully quiet.
-It's how I think.
[chuckles softly]
[inhales deeply]
By the way,
the pictures are already in the cloud.
Whatever you're thinking,
don't get any ideas.
Stop talking down to me.
One perk of a power trip is doing that.
-[chuckles]
-[sighs]
Tell me what happened. I need to know.
She spent three months
in production together.
That color doesn't suit you.
[Mi-do]  Even hidden under a scarf and hat,
I recognized her right away.
[intriguing piano music playing]
-[laughs] You know… Oh!
-Oh, no. I'm sorry. I'm such an idiot.
-Oh. [pants] Oh, forgive me.
-Don't worry. I'll do it. Give me some…
-[Mi-do] Gosh.
-[Ji-yeon] Do you have any napkins?
-[chuckles nervously]
-I'm sorry.
At first, I thought you were
the guy she was seeing.
Your fancy suit, the watch and shoes,
they are exactly like his.
-[scoffs]
-Turns out that you're a bigger deal.
All right, just tell me what you want.
Let's start with an apology.
-[sighs]
-[music concludes]
I shouldn't have smashed your phone
on the ground.
Not that. Come on, try harder.
Uh… Is this about your family and your ex?
Yes. You said
he was a piece of shit, right?
He's a good person.
You had no right to say that.
[scoffs]
-You're not together, are you?
-He doesn't deserve your disrespect.
Wow. True love.
Still so affectionate
even after the breakup.
-All right, I apologize.
-[exhales]
Now, stop acting like a child
and tell me what you want.
Double my directing fee.
-[intriguing music playing]
-[scoffs]
[Mi-do] A co-director credit.
Fifty percent ownership of the IP.
Ah, and articles regarding my resignation
will have to go through me
before they're released.
A week should be enough time.
[music concludes]
HUNMIN CONFECTIONERY R&D CENTER
Hey, Sang-hun.
I'm at Incheon Research Center
for a department meeting.
The consumer feedback survey
compared to the sensory test…
Hey, can we talk for a minute? Huh?
I… I can't be the only one who thinks
that we have a thing, right?
[Su-a] It was only a business lunch.
Don't read too much into it.
You… You call that a business lunch?
Yeah.
[Yeon-ho]
You asked me out on a Friday night
because you wanted to hear
about grub infestations
-in the sweet potato fields?
-Yeah.
[scoffs]
Since we mainly use sweet potatoes,
I needed to study them thoroughly.
And because you handle the production,
I thought I needed your opinion.
Who asks for a professional opinion
on a Friday night?
[sighs]
Look, I have no personal interest.
Don't reach out
unless it's work-related, okay?
Uh…
Oh, God damn it. [sighs]
-[footsteps receding]
-[door opens]
-[Su-a sighs]
-[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[Su-a] Can I have a smoke, please?
These are kind of strong.
I smoke those. Raven Blue.
The guy who taught me to smoke
in high school liked that brand.
Sounds like a punk.
Giving this crap to a high school kid.
Let's head to the meeting now.
-[footsteps receding]
-[scoffs]
[intriguing music playing]
What is the point of switching
from perilla to sesame in  goguma  chips?
Remind me.
Well, whether we like it or not,
we need to change the ingredient.
The monsoon wiped out
the perilla crops last season,
so we don't have any other choice.
Besides, the research team
approved using sesame instead.
[Su-a] The board meeting's in two days.
-There's no time for tasting.
-[laughs]
Let's get everyone else's opinion.
Uh, are you all on board with the change?
-[employee 1] I can't really tell.
-It tastes the same, honestly.
-[employee 2] It's not bad at all, yeah.
-Yeah.
You see? Su-a, the consumers
won't even be able to tell the difference.
Let's move on.
[Namgung] Well, there's definitely
an acidic aftertaste.
[music fades]
Sesame has a high unsaturated fat content.
It spoils faster.
Which leaves a bad aftertaste,
if you ask me.
-If there's an issue with ingredients…
-[sighs]
…I believe we can talk it through
and find common ground.
If we need to change the mix ratio,
we'll share the data
with the purchasing department, right?
I hope you'll understand.
Of course, that makes sense.
That's the protocol from now on.
But we need to let it slide this time.
We don't have time
to make a new seasoning. [sighs]
I'll produce it, sir.
-[quirky piano music playing]
-[cutlery clinking]
-[sighs] All right, spit it out.
-The imported sweet potatoes.
You reported it to Manager Yoon Jae-mun,
did you not?
No, I did not.
If you can't trust your direct superior,
you could have reported it to Audit.
Too many people are involved, so…
with no hard evidence,
like the Distribution Team bribery case,
only a couple of pawns
would take the fall.
[chuckles] Obviously,
it's a very dangerous case,
-and you want to drag me into it.
-I was getting lonely.
I shouldn't have told you.
[cutlery clinking continues]
[Namgung sighs]
[gasps]
Among the people involved, is there anyone
you're personally connected to?
Maybe a… a blood relative or, uh,
an irreconcilable family dispute,
and you are simply in pursuit of revenge,
and that's your motivation?
I'm truly sorry to disappoint,
but that is not my motivation.
Huh.
You're climbing up the ladder.
You'd be the youngest executive
moving up ranks--
I'm not moving up ranks.
You're doing this just because?
That makes no sense to me.
[inhales deeply] It's just my nature.
Hmm. I can't ignore what I've seen.
If I latch onto a case,
I have to get to the bottom of it.
I keep digging and following every lead.
It's not out of justice
or a sense of duty.
-So, I'm just an awkward kind of girl.
-[music concludes]
Okay, I get the point.
If that's how strongly you feel,
I will respect that.
-[sighs]
-[cutlery clinking]
You know this is Kitchen Lab 3, right?
Ah, you didn't know.
You shouldn't be here by yourself.
They say this kitchen's haunted.
It's not just a rumor.
-I saw a lot while working here.
-I don't mind.
-I'd kick the ghost's ass.
-Oh.
Please say hi for me if you see the ghost.
-Ask how it's doing.
-Yeah, I will.
[scoffs]
-[footsteps receding]
-[door opens]
[door closes]
-[sighs]
-[indistinct chatter]
[cell phone vibrating]
Oh, hey.
[quirky instrumental music plays, fades]
CONTEST FOR ENGAGED COUPLES
[laughs awkwardly]
Well, a couples event is being hosted
at the wedding hall tonight.
-[Wan-do] Whoo!
-[Yeong-do] And I signed you guys up.
-[whimsical music playing]
-[chuckles] They're having contests,
-and you two are sure to win.
-[Wan-do] You can get a prize.
Can you believe fifth place gets ginseng?
I mean, newlyweds,
they're tired day and night.
When it comes to energy,
red ginseng is the safest bet.
-Yeah, it's the money choice.
-[Yeong-do] The money choice.
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Fourth place, a Bellafino coffee machine.
Its foam is just so beautiful.
Oh, just imagine having
a delicious espresso every morning.
Delicious. You like coffee.
-I know you do.
-[Yeong-do] She loves it.
Third place, Humiel 20-liter dehumidifier.
Man, during the rainy season,
you won't even know it's raining.
So soft and dry.
And second, Airponic Dress Care.
You wear your shirts daily,
the collars get dirty.
Will you wash them every day? Huh?
-Huh? [gasps]
-[groans softly]
-[hesitates]
-And first, the robot vacuum cleaner.
[bell dinging sound effect]
Top of the line
with AI navigation and mopping.
[music builds]
-So, what do you think?
-A robot vacuum. It does it all.
Mobbing and self-navigation. Huh?
-A robot vacuum.
-For real.
[Yeong-do] We don't even need first place.
-Just get the red ginseng, man.
-[music concludes]
[host] Now, let's begin the one and only
amazing engaged couples event.
Let's hear it for
-the couples joining us today.
-["Heart Beat Supersonic" playing]
BUSINESS COUPLE
-[all cheering, applauding]
-Good luck! [laughs]
-[sighs]
-We split it 50-50.
-Don't you change your mind later.
-You too.
[host] We have incredible prizes tonight.
-♪ Your heart beat supersonic ♪
-[song concludes]
TELEPATHY
And now for the first question.
In the morning,
what website does your boyfriend visit
-every single day as he wakes up?
-[chuckles softly]
I bet she knows the answer.
-What do you think? Huh? What? Yeah.
-[host] Three, two, one.
Now, your answers.
BUSINESS COUPLE
TODAY'S DEALS
-[crowd cheering, applauding]
-Oh, that's right!
-Nice!
-That's right!
-That's Lee! You got this, sis!
-[Wan-do] Yeah!
What is your girlfriend's
weirdest sleeping habit?
-[upbeat rock music playing]
-[host] Now, answers!
DOING A FULL 360
-[crowd cheering, applauding]
-[overlapping chatter]
We wanna know what is
your all-time favorite karaoke song?
Oh, yeah!
A THOUSAND-YEAR LOVE
-[crowd cheering, applauding]
-[overlapping chatter]
SPEED QUIZ
KEYWORD: BICYCLE
I bought you this thing
for our fifth anniversary.
We ended up having a fight
because you lost it.
-My necklace!
-That was for our third anniversary.
-Uh…
-Uh, when you were in second grade.
-You broke your leg because of this.
-[gasps]
-Every day I carry you.
-Bicycle?
-[crowd cheering, applauding]
-Yes! Yeah.
-Oh! Who do you hate most in the world?
-Lee Yeong-do.
-Different term.
-A scrounger.
-[Namgung] Other word.
-[Mi-do] A scumbag. A psychopath.
A total jerk. A future loner!
-Oh, my God!
-[music stops]
[pants]
Oh, you said, rather bite your tongue
than call him that.
-A brother.
-[music resumes]
KEYWORD: BROTHER
-Yes!
-[cheers]
-[crowd cheering, applauding]
-[both sigh]
TELEPATHY ORIGAMI
Fold it up, so the corner
touches the top, okay?
-[Namgung] Right.
-Now, fold both sides
-into a perfect triangle from the center.
-Uh-huh.
Next, fold the top and both ends back.
-Done.
-Okay?
-Here.
-[gasps]
-[music concludes]
-[host] And now it's time
for today's most exciting game,
a heart rate test.
1ST: BUSINESS COUPLE, 520 POINTS
-It's called "Steal My Heart."
-[heart rate monitor beeping]
[host] This game
can easily turn the tables
simply because this round's
final score depends entirely
on your combined heart rate.
You'll look into your partner's eyes
for one full minute.
Take your positions and…
-[audience applauding]
-[Yeong-do] Let's go!
-[Wan-do] You've gotta win.
-[host] Look into your partner's eyes.
Can you feel your hearts racing?
-They're doing it. They're doing it.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh!
[host] In this game,
there's no fooling anyone.
-[Wan-do] There we go.
-[Yeong-do] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-[Wan-do] You've got this!
-[host] Oh, look at those heart rates.
-They're already rising.
-[overlapping chatter]
[host] Those hearts
are pounding strong right now.
[laughs] Oh.
BUSINESS COUPLE
-[Yeong-do] Oh, no.
-[poignant piano music playing]
[host] Oh! Those numbers,
look at them, they're dropping.
-Oh, no. They were overwhelmingly…
-[heart rate monitors beeping]
…in first place just a moment ago.
I'm not feeling the chemistry
between you two.
[indistinct chatter]
-[cashier] Is that all?
-Yeah.
-[scanner beeps]
-[automated voice]  Please take your prize.
Oh, you have a free gift, Hot Choco Chips.
When this first came out,
everyone went crazy for it.
Nowadays, they give them out
as free gifts.
[scanner beeps]
[scoffs]
[can lid pops]
[Mi-do]  You may not believe it,
but there was a time
when we were like that.
Every moment was passionate and exciting.
And we only had eyes for each other.
Those were the days
when our love shone the brightest.
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
Director Bong Joon-ho's film,  Parasite,
surpassed ten million viewers
in just 53 days since its release,
breaking box office records…
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
…both domestically and internationally,
it's proving both its cinematic quality
and mass appeal,
breaking yet another record
in Korean cinema history.
[fan whirring]
[Namgung] I'll come visit you
every weekend.
Actually, no.
-I'll come every Friday after work.
-[Mi-do] Don't do that.
You'll be too tired.
It's a ten-hour round trip.
[gasps]
-You've changed. Don't you miss me?
-I'm just saying you'll be tired.
No, you're different now.
When I ask you something,
you reply with a…
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
[Namgung] I'm serious.
No, what do you mean? I'll just go, "Oh."
[chuckles] Seriously,
what else would I say?
-You can go, "Mm-mm-mm."
-[gasps]
-[Namgung] You used to do that too.
-When did I ever go like,
"Mm-hmm." Of course not.
[in higher pitch] "Mm-hmm."
[in normal voice] That's you.
-Do it again.
-Mm. Mm-hmm.
-Again.
-[Mi-do] Okay, you need to stop.
-All right. [chuckles]
-[giggles] You're crazy.
[giggles]
-[music fades]
-Hmm. The place is kind of cool.
-The four of us are sharing a room now.
-That's a relief.
[sighs] I miss you already.
-How about a selfie?
-No, selfies aren't the real you.
-Hey!
-[laughs]
-[groans] I can't wait until the weekend.
-Mm. [chuckles softly]
-Uh--
-By working hard.
-[chuckles]
-I'll call you later.
-[cell phone beeps]
-Are you allowed to call your girlfriend
while waiting for the potatoes?
I'm sorry, sir.
I've already finished the seasoning.
Once the potatoes arrive,
I just need to mix them.
-Hmm. Okay.
-Hmm.
-[footsteps receding]
-[breathes deeply]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pattering]
[groans]
[sighs]
-Oh!
-[eerie music playing]
[gasps, yelps]
[thunder rumbling continues]
-[rattling]
-[thunder rumbles]
-[Namgung gasps softly]
-[music intensifies]
Spooky.
-[gasps, exclaims]
-[eerie musical sting]
[music fades]
Namgung! [giggles]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[giggles]
What? Why are you just standing there?
[gasps] Are you happy?
Hmm? Hmm? Mm-hmm. [giggles]
-Why are you here? And the shoot?
-The rain forced us to cancel.
I caught a ride
with the staff heading to Incheon.
-But how did you get in here?
-[chuckles]
Ta-da. I spooked this guy away. [giggles]
[exhales sharply]
We were short on extras today.
We had to fill in.
That's why I look like this.
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm.
[groans] What's with this boring reaction?
Should I just leave? Hmm.
I'll go now. I'm gonna go. Hmm?
[sighs] You're so mean.
I'm gonna kill you.
You almost gave me
a heart attack a minute ago.
Never again.
Your reaction was so underwhelming
that it's not allowed anymore.
I'm gonna get you.
What kind of boring welcome was that?
Hmm? Such a buzzkill.
[inhales sharply] You actually need
to react so that I can--
[passionate guitar music playing]
[Mi-do moans softly]
[Namgung breathes sharply]
[objects clattering]
[both moan softly]
-[Mi-do moans softly]
-[objects clattering]
-[bowl clattering]
-[both moan softly]
-[music stops]
[quirky upbeat music playing]
-What do we do? Who is that?
-Here, here.
[rattling]
-Oh, sir, I thought you were gone.
-Uh… [hesitates]
Yeah, I was, but…
-let's just leave together, hmm?
-[music fades]
-Hurry, let's just clock out.
-Uh, no, wait.
-Sir, I'm not finished mixing yet.
-Huh?
-What? Oh, jeez…
-[chuckles nervously]
…you should have finished
that mix hours ago.
Uh…
[Ho-sik] Wait. Hmm?
Why is your mix that color?
Hmm?
What? Is that dark chocolate
with capsaicin in the container there?
Uh, yeah. Uh, when I tasted that,
it lacked character,
-but I tried with…
-[Ho-sik] Oh, wow.
That mix of dark chocolate
and capsaicin is quite interesting.
-Oh. Mm. It's pretty good.
-Huh?
[Ho-sik] Very impressive.
Mm-hmm. It's intriguing.
Here, try it. Wow, it's like…
It goes really well with the spiciness.
It's like the sweetness
wraps around the heat.
-[object clatters]
-[Ho-sik] Mm-hmm.
-[quirky music playing]
-[thunder rumbling]
[eerie music overlapping]
What… Who is she?
-Who? Where?
-That girl right there.
She's by the window.
-She's v… very well-dressed, but…
-By the window? Where, sir?
-Can't-- I mean…
-You see her? Right there.
Her blouse is like, uh…
She's wearing a black skirt and long hair.
-Oh. Sorry, sir. I don't see anyone.
-[Ho-sik] What do you mean you can't?
-Who… Now, she's starting to smile.
-[music intensifies]
-Look, she's smiling.
-[thunder rumbling]
[yells] Oh, God, I… I'm leaving.
[whimpers] I'm gonna…
-[whimpers]
-[imitates ghost moaning]
-[Ho-sik screaming]
-[music fades]
-[whispers] He's gonna be okay.
-[Ho-sik screaming fades]
Believe it or not, he's the strongest mind
in the company.
-Mi-do, try this.
-[Mi-do] Huh?
-Mm. Wow. Amazing. [munches]
-Like it?
-Mm-hmm. I kind of love it.
-[Namgung chuckles softly]
Wow, it's really good. [munches] Mm.
What?
-Why did you cry today?
-Hmm? I didn't cry.
Come on. Why did you cry?
[groans] What do you mean?
Hmm. It rained, so the shoot got canceled.
I'm quite happy and really excited
to see you tonight.
Why did you cry? Tell me.
[breathes heavily, sobs]
-[sentimental piano music playing]
-[sobs]
The assistant director is so mean.
-He's always doing that to the crew…
-What?
-[Mi-do sniffles]
-Somebody has to stop that guy.
-[Mi-do sobs]
-And then?
So, he pinned the blame on me
because things weren't ready. [sobs]
You should have pushed back.
It wasn't your fault.
If you quit now,
you'll only prove that guy right.
[sobs] What can I do?
He's so rude and he's always
raising his voice to everyone.
-[sighs]
-[Mi-do sobs]
[Namgung] Is that jerk on set now?
-I'll get him.
-[sobs] No!
No, if you do that,
I'll die of embarrassment. [sobs]
Listen, if I cause a scene,
I know you'll look dumb.
-[sobs]
-But staying quiet
-makes you look dumb too.
-[sobs]
Even if you decide to quit,
they should know what you think.
[whimpers]
Running away like this
isn't the Mi-do I know.
-[sobs]
-Let's go. Together.
[cries]
-[music fades]
-[sighs] What do we do now?
-We can't get 500 people by tomorrow.
-[indistinct chatter]
It overlaps with  Sonata of the Wind.
[sighs] The schedule plainly showed
that the shoot was on the 28th.
That was the old schedule,
but it was reworked.
-Excuse me?
-Um, no, wait, I think so.
-I'm pretty sure that's right.
-[Mi-do] Did you mess up again?
-[Seung-ho] You again?
-What now?
There's no staff left for you to blame.
But don't worry.
I'm not here to tell the rest of the crew
you ordered the set torn down
and screwed the schedule.
[hesitates] Who the hell asked you?
You fucking crazy?
Let me tell you what,
you'll never debut as a director.
I've seen that short film of yours.
I finally understood
why you act like that.
[sighs]
You're consumed by an inferiority complex.
Last thing I want is to be like you.
Stealing angles and storyboards
and losing your identity.
I won't end up
a has-been chasing movie premieres.
I owe you. Thanks to you,
I know I'll be a great director one day.
Hey, did you hear what she just said?
How dare you talk like that?
-[crew member] Whoa! Sir, sir, sir, sir!
-I'm not--
-She insulted me!
-[overlapping chatter]
Hey, you! You're a nobody, bitch!
You'll never make it! You're nothing!
It was an amazing honor, sir.
Thanks for the opportunity.
[sighs] Five hundred.
-Huh?
-If you gather 500 extras by tomorrow,
I'll appoint you my assistant director.
So, can you do it?
[gasps softly]
-[walkie-talkie beeps]
-[Gyeong-su] Get ready.
-Action!
-[crew member] Rolling!
[tense dramatic music playing]
-[explosion]
-[indistinct shouting, clamoring]
-[gunfire]
-[explosions]
-[gunfire continues]
-[indistinct shouting, clamoring]
-[music fades]
-[indistinct clamoring continues faintly]
How did you know?
[gunfire continues faintly]
-You've known since we were young.
-[explosion]
You can always tell when I cry.
Not even my own mom could tell.
And you always know.
Honestly…
-I just know.
-[chuckles softly]
I'm good at telling…
when you're suffering.
[breathes deeply]
-[explosions, gunfire continue faintly]
-[indistinct clamoring continues faintly]
Yes, and cut, and cut.
What are those two doing?
Huh?
[indistinct clamoring, screaming]
-[gentle guitar music playing]
-[vocalist singing in Korean]
Hey! Lee Mi-do! Cut! Stop!
[grunts] These fucking kids!
Huh? Oh, no, cut!
Cut! I said cut! Cut now! Hey! Cut! Cut!
Why are those two idiots still there?
-Huh? Get out of my way!
-[crew member] Sir, please!
[Gyeong-su] Hey! No! Fuck!
Why are you stopping me?
They're in danger!
[continues shouting indistinctly]
…get them out
before the whole set goes and blows up!
[Mi-do]  Our movie ended up
becoming the biggest hit of the year.
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
Today, Oh Gyeong-su's
When That Day Comes
officially crossed the ten million mark,
becoming the highest-grossing film
of the year.
[indistinct chatter]
[Mi-do]  The snack we created was
eventually launched as Hot Choco Chips…
HOT CHOCO CHIPS SOLD OUT
…and sold out almost instantly,
triggering a massive shortage.
It made 30 billion won
in only three months.
Hunmin Confectionery's stock price
skyrocketed that year.
HOT CHOCO CHIPS SOLD OUT
[Mi-do]  And our love was taking flight
into worlds beyond imagination.
[both pant]
[both smooching]
[clears throat]
-[coughs, clears throat]
-[giggles softly]
-[pan sizzling]
-[both smooch]
[cutlery clinking]
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
[music fades]
[Mi-do]  Where did all that passion
we once shared go?
And the butterflies,
where did they fly away to?
Where did we lose our way?
[sighs]
[pants]
-[sign beeping]
-[footsteps running]
-Oh!
-[car horn honking]
-[gasps, breathes heavily]
-[grunts, gasps]
-[car horns honking]
[breathes shakily, inhales]
-[car horn honking]
-[grunts softly, gasps]
[breathes heavily]
[shouts] Have you lost it?
[breathes deeply]
Why did you cry today?
Why were you crying?
What happened this time?
Why do you always have…
I get worried when you cry!
[Seung-ho] Director Lee Mi-do?
Wow, it's been a while.
I almost didn't recognize you.
How are you?
-Good.
-And how are you doing, Director?
Well, you know, working a lot. Crazy busy.
Are you here for my premiere?
THE UNINVITED GUEST
[chuckles] I'll introduce you.
Uh, he's our production CEO
and one of the investors.
INFINITE RUSH
NA SEUNG-HO
-[film investor] Hi.
-[Seung-ho] This is Director Lee Mi-do.
I'm sure you all know her.
After  Spring Comes Winter,
the 13th season.
[film investor] Ah.
-[chuckles]
-[chuckles softly]
So, Mi-do,
funny how life comes full circle.
Remember you once told me
that I'd never make my feature film debut?
Turns out the one who never debuted
was actually you.
Those words hit hard back then,
and I'd really like
to return the favor now.
Lee Mi-do, you're never gonna make
your feature film debut.
You've lost momentum.
You've lost your passion.
That's why you're gonna fade
into obscurity.
And now…
enjoy my film.
[poignant instrumental music playing]
[sniffles] Well,
that's none of your business now.
-Just don't worry about that!
-I wish I could stop!
-[breathes heavily]
-I don't want to care anymore!
And yet here we are again.
Just face it. We are done now.
[sighs]
Mi-do…
let's try again.
[sighs]
-If we put in the effort--
-Listen to me, Namgung!
If only I could, I'd hit the reset button,
but that's not an option.
I wish I could go back
when you were all that I needed.
But I can't go back, can I?
[breathes deeply] Namgung…
wanna know what our future looks like?
I'll become a burden to you…
and you'll smother me with care.
Maybe in three,
or five, or even ten years…
we'll keep trying to make it work.
But, Namgung…
in the end, we… come to hate each other.
Maybe…
Maybe we already do
and just haven't noticed.
Namgung, I couldn't take it.
I couldn't bear you hating me,
and I could never bear hating you.
I see that future ahead.
And I can't let us end up hurt
and trapped like that.
Why?
Does that scare you?
Are you scared of that future?
Does it scare you more than losing me?
Mm. It does. Doesn't it terrify you?
Of course.
I'm scared too.
But…
I can't just let you go.
I can't lose you so suddenly.
That fear brings me to my knees.
[sighs softly]
[Namgung] Listen, I…
Mi-do, I…
I'll go wherever you go.
[sobs softly]
No matter where it takes us.
I choose you even if it destroys us.
I still wanna be with you.
[sighs]
[poignant instrumental music continues]
Let's get engaged.
-Marry me, Mi-do.
-[music fades]
-Please, let's get married.
-[dramatic rock music playing]
[vocalist singing in Korean]
♪ I hear your voice in the quiet night… ♪
THANK YOU TO CHO HAN-CHEUL, KIM DA-HUIN,
AND OH DONG-MIN
FOR THEIR SPECIAL APPEARANCE
WHEN THAT DAY COMES
MI-DO
[Mi-do]  Namgung,
I really wanna feel butterflies for you.
And I really want you
to feel them for me, too.
[Suk-hee] His name is Namgung.
From now on, he'll be living with us.
You should talk to Hoya about this.
[Su-a]  Nice to meet you.
I'm Park Su-a.
I look forward to collaborating.
-[gasps]
-[Namgung]  You are so much clingier
-than I expected.
-[Su-a]  Namgung, this is clearly wrong.
[Mi-do]  I looked into your background.
You do whatever Seo Ju-hyeok
tells you to do.
[Tae-seung]  So, I'm a dog?
[Namgung]  Hey, look at you now.
-♪ I'm reaching out ♪
-[music concludes]